## CHANGCHANG LIU



Portfolio: changchangl.com

Cell: 217-979-6985

Email: changchang.liu115@gmail.com Address: 3063 Teal Ridge Ct., San Jose, CA

Changchang is a self-motivated, versatile and passionate designer who's been developing impactful design since 2008. She believes in egoless collaboration, unstoppable grit, the infinite exquisiteness...

And above all, empathy.

## **EXPERIENCES**

Jul 2016 - Present

ROKU INC. @ Los Gatos, CA | Sr. Product Designer

- + Collaborate with Engineers, and Project Managers to design OS on Roku platform.
- + Deliver new products that span all project phases, from concept and design to production
- + Refine and deliver a holistic design language, and explore a variety of design directions in a rapid iterative fashion

Nov 2014 - Aug 2017

**STARTUP PROJECTS** @ All Cross the World | UI/UX Design Consultant

- + Clients are from all over the world-- US, China, South Korea etc.
- + Projects cover a wide range-- from mobile to desktop; from B2B, B2C to O2O (SaaS, education, fashion and tools...)

Oct 2014 - Jul 2016

BLASEN LANDSCAPE ARCHITECTURE @ San Anselmo, CA | Rendering Specialist/ Designer

- + High-end Residential Design for TOP Billionaires
- + AT&T Ball Park Giants Garden

Jun 2013 - May 2014

UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS - URBANA CHAMPAIGN | Teaching + Research + Graduate Assitant

- + Teaching assistant of Design Communications
- + Research assitant of Urban Design Department on Resort Renovation
- + Graduate assitant of Design Profession Study

Jun 2008 - May 2012

LX Studio @ Chengdu, China | Graphic Designer

## **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS - URBANA CHAMPAIGN | Master of Fine and Applied Arts

UC SAN DIEGO | Certificate, User Experience: Research & Prototyping

TECHBOW BOOTCAMP @ Sunnyvale, CA | UX/ UI Design Bootcamp

**BOCCONI UNIVERSITY** @ Milan, Italy | Certificate, Fashion and Luxury Management

SICHUAN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY @ Chengdu, China | B.S., Landscape Architecture

## **SKILLS**

Design

TV OS/ Web/ Mobile Design, Print, Illustration, Branding, Typograhy, Motion, 3D, Prototype, Story Board...

Software

Adobe Creative Suite (Ps, Ai, Ae, Id); UX/ UI Kit (Sketch, flinto, figma); 3D (Cinema4D, 3Ds Max, SketchUp)

Coding

XML, basic HTML, CSS